



About Me

Experienced Frontend developer, Passionate web development trainer, Dedicated self-learner with a passion for problem-solving, consistently acquiring new knowledge through free online resources such as FreeCodeCamp, W3Schools, and YouTube tutorials.

Contact



+91 9943567950

manthonysuresh@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/anthony-m1995/

363, South street, Elaynkanni, Thandrampet, Tiruvannamalai, Tamil Nadu - 606753



Education

2013 - 2017

Completed B.E Mechanical Eng., in Mahendra Engineering College, Namakkal with CGPA 8.23

2011 - 2012

Completed HSC in Carmel Hrs. Sec. School, Elayankanni with 79.8%

2009 - 2010

Completed SSLC in Carmel Hrs. Sec. School, Elayankanni with 74%

Anthony M Front End Developer



https://anthonym995.github.io/portfolio/

Experience

FREELANCE FRONTEND DEVELOPER & TRAINER - APR 2022 - Present

Self-employed/TV.malai - Created dynamic web apps, Collaborated with clients to meet project requirements, maintenance, support, and development tasks. Proficient in Git, managing project repos on GitHub.

FRONTEND DEVELPOER - AUG 2021 - MAR 2022

Billionapps Infotech Solutions/Chennai - Developing pixel perfect responsive web design & web application, Converting Adobe XD, Figma design to web application and API intergration.

FRONTEND DEVELOPER - JULY 2020 - JULY 2021

Itechuniversal/Chennai - Developing pixel perfect responsive web design and web application, Bootstrap, jQuery, Git, Adobe Xd.

Professional Skills

HTML5/CSS3	
Javascript	
React.js/Redux	
Bootstrap	
Node.js	
Photoshop	

Additional Skills

Linux Distro	MongoDB	Express.js	Tailwind
Less/Scss	Git,GitHub	AdobeXd	MS Excell

Hobbies

Mobile Games Playing Chess Rubik's Cube **Listening Songs**

Personal details

Date of Birth : 28/05/1995 Marital Status: Married

Father's Name: Magimainathan Mother's Name: Francismary

Languages : Tamil, English, Hindi